{"BS20 6AQ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "7352", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "7", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "10", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "11", "Anaemias": "8", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "6", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "4", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "6", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "12", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "7", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "8", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "7", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "5", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "6", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "7", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "11", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "5", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "7", "Other diseases of intestines": "17", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "4", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "8", "Arthropathies": "16", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "8", "Soft tissue disorders": "6", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "7", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "27", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "6", "Congenital malformations": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "11", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "14", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "8", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "5", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "5", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "6", "Examination and investigation": "8", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "14", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS3 1AS": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "14618", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "8", "Certain bacterial diseases": "8", "Viral infections characterized by skin & mucous mem. lesns.": "1", "Other viral diseases": "6", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "14", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "8", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "11", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "10", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "20", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "22", "Anaemias": "15", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "5", "Disorders of thyroid gland": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "3", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "12", "Dementia": "1", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "3", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "2", "Other degenerative diseases (incl. Alzheimer).": "1", "Extrapyramidal & movement disorders (incl. Parkinsonism).": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "3", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "7", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "7", "Cerebral palsy & other paralytic syndromes": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "12", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "23", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "4", "Rheumatic heart disease": "1", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "13", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "16", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "6", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "3", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "5", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "2", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "8", "Influenza & pneumonia": "15", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "9", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "5", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "12", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "4", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "13", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "22", "Diseases of appendix": "2", "Hernia": "10", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "13", "Other diseases of intestines": "33", "Diseases of liver": "2", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "11", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "7", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "17", "Dermatitis and eczema": "1", "Papulosquamous disorders (including Psoriasis)": "1", "Urticaria and erythems": "1", "Arthropathies": "31", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "16", "Soft tissue disorders": "13", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "5", "Other disorders of the musculoskeletal system & conn. tiss.": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "4", "Renal failure": "5", "Urolithiasis": "5", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "14", "Diseases of male genital organs": "6", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "11", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "6", "Complications of labour and delivery": "54", "Delivery": "2", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "13", "Congenital malformations": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "22", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "28", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "5", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "4", "General symptoms & signs": "16", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "10", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "2", "Injuries to the head": "9", "Injuries to the neck": "1", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "2", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "2", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "4", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "5", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "4", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "4", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Burns and corrosions": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "6", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "11", "Examination and investigation": "16", "Potential health hazards related to communicable diseases": "1", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "27", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "6", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1", "Persons with potential health hazards related to family": "1"}}, "BS11 9SB": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4369", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "16", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS14 8PT": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3932", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "9", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "8", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "14", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS6 5PT": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "8486", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "5", "Certain bacterial diseases": "5", "Viral infections characterized by skin & mucous mem. lesns.": "1", "Other viral diseases": "4", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "8", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "11", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "13", "Anaemias": "9", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "3", "Diabetes Mellitus": "2", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "7", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "2", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "4", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "4", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "7", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "13", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "8", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "9", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "3", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "5", "Influenza & pneumonia": "9", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "5", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "7", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "3", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "8", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "13", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "6", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "8", "Other diseases of intestines": "19", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "6", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "4", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "10", "Arthropathies": "18", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "9", "Soft tissue disorders": "7", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "3", "Diseases of the kidney": "3", "Renal failure": "3", "Urolithiasis": "3", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "8", "Diseases of male genital organs": "4", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "6", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "4", "Complications of labour and delivery": "31", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "7", "Congenital malformations": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "13", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "16", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "3", "General symptoms & signs": "9", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "6", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "5", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "3", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "3", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "6", "Examination and investigation": "9", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "16", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "4", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS16 3TD": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4371", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "16", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS36 2DE": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "5658", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "8", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "8", "Anaemias": "6", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "9", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "5", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "6", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "6", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "5", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "8", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "4", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "5", "Other diseases of intestines": "13", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "6", "Arthropathies": "12", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "6", "Soft tissue disorders": "5", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "5", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "4", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "21", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "5", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "11", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "6", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "6", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "11", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3"}}, "BS5 0UA": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6594", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "9", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "10", "Anaemias": "7", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "10", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "6", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "7", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "7", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "6", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "10", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "5", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "6", "Other diseases of intestines": "15", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "8", "Arthropathies": "14", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "7", "Soft tissue disorders": "6", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "6", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "24", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "6", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "10", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "13", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "7", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "7", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "12", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS23 1YA": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4852", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "7", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "8", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "11", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "6", "Arthropathies": "10", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "5", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "4", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "18", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "9", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS9 3AA": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4254", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "16", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS35 1DP": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "2074", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "1", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "3", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "3", "Anaemias": "2", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "3", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "2", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "1", "Influenza & pneumonia": "2", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "1", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "2", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "3", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "1", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "2", "Other diseases of intestines": "5", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "2", "Arthropathies": "4", "Dorsopathies": "2", "Soft tissue disorders": "2", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "2", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "8", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "2", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "2", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "2", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "4", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS34 6BQ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "5756", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "8", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "9", "Anaemias": "6", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "9", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "5", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "6", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "6", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "5", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "9", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "4", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "5", "Other diseases of intestines": "13", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "7", "Arthropathies": "12", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "6", "Soft tissue disorders": "5", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "5", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "4", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "21", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "5", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "11", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "6", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "6", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "11", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3"}}, "BS25 1AF": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3758", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "8", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "8", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "14", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS7 9RR": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6950", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "9", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "10", "Anaemias": "7", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "6", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "6", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "11", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "6", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "8", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "7", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "6", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "6", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "10", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "5", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "6", "Other diseases of intestines": "16", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "8", "Arthropathies": "15", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "8", "Soft tissue disorders": "6", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "7", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "25", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "6", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "11", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "13", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "8", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "5", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "8", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "13", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS5 6SA": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "2020", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "1", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "3", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "3", "Anaemias": "2", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "3", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "2", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "2", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "1", "Influenza & pneumonia": "2", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "1", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "2", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "3", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "1", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "2", "Other diseases of intestines": "5", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "1", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "2", "Arthropathies": "4", "Dorsopathies": "2", "Soft tissue disorders": "2", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "2", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "1", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "7", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "2", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "2", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "1", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "2", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "4", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS37 4DQ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "5708", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "8", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "9", "Anaemias": "6", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "9", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "5", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "6", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "6", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "5", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "9", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "4", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "5", "Other diseases of intestines": "13", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "7", "Arthropathies": "12", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "6", "Soft tissue disorders": "5", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "5", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "4", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "21", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "5", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "11", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "6", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "6", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "11", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3"}}, "BS16 5SG": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "10207", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "6", "Certain bacterial diseases": "6", "Viral infections characterized by skin & mucous mem. lesns.": "1", "Other viral diseases": "4", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "10", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "8", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "7", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "14", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "15", "Anaemias": "11", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "3", "Disorders of thyroid gland": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "2", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "8", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "2", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Extrapyramidal & movement disorders (incl. Parkinsonism).": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "5", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "5", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "8", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "16", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "3", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "9", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "11", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "4", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "3", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "6", "Influenza & pneumonia": "10", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "6", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "4", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "8", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "3", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "9", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "15", "Diseases of appendix": "2", "Hernia": "7", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "9", "Other diseases of intestines": "23", "Diseases of liver": "2", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "8", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "5", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "12", "Arthropathies": "22", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "11", "Soft tissue disorders": "9", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "3", "Diseases of the kidney": "3", "Renal failure": "3", "Urolithiasis": "3", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "10", "Diseases of male genital organs": "4", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "7", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "4", "Complications of labour and delivery": "37", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "9", "Congenital malformations": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "16", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "20", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "4", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "3", "General symptoms & signs": "11", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "7", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "2", "Injuries to the head": "7", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "2", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "3", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "3", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "3", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "3", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "4", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "8", "Examination and investigation": "11", "Potential health hazards related to communicable diseases": "1", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "19", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "5", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS7 0LS": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "20", "diagnoses": {}}, "BS30 5QQ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3700", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "8", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "8", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "14", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS14 0SU": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6511", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "9", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "10", "Anaemias": "7", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "10", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "6", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "7", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "7", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "6", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "10", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "5", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "6", "Other diseases of intestines": "15", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "7", "Arthropathies": "14", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "7", "Soft tissue disorders": "6", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "6", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "24", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "6", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "10", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "13", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "7", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "7", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "12", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS4 4HU": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3226", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "4", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "5", "Anaemias": "3", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "5", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "5", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "7", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "7", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "12", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "6", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS48 2XX": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "12767", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "7", "Certain bacterial diseases": "7", "Viral infections characterized by skin & mucous mem. lesns.": "1", "Other viral diseases": "5", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "12", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "7", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "10", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "9", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "17", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "19", "Anaemias": "13", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "4", "Disorders of thyroid gland": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "3", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "10", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "2", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "2", "Extrapyramidal & movement disorders (incl. Parkinsonism).": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "6", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "6", "Cerebral palsy & other paralytic syndromes": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "10", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "20", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "4", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "12", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "14", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "5", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "3", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "4", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "7", "Influenza & pneumonia": "13", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "8", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "5", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "11", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "4", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "12", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "19", "Diseases of appendix": "2", "Hernia": "9", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "11", "Other diseases of intestines": "29", "Diseases of liver": "2", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "9", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "6", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "15", "Dermatitis and eczema": "1", "Papulosquamous disorders (including Psoriasis)": "1", "Arthropathies": "27", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "14", "Soft tissue disorders": "11", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "4", "Diseases of the kidney": "4", "Renal failure": "4", "Urolithiasis": "4", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "12", "Diseases of male genital organs": "6", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "9", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "5", "Complications of labour and delivery": "47", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "11", "Congenital malformations": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "20", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "25", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "5", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "4", "General symptoms & signs": "14", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "8", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "2", "Injuries to the head": "8", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "2", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "2", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "3", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "4", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "4", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "3", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Burns and corrosions": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "5", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "10", "Examination and investigation": "14", "Potential health hazards related to communicable diseases": "1", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "24", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "6", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS34 5TF": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4001", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "9", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "8", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "15", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS10 6SP": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "8117", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "8", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "11", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "12", "Anaemias": "8", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "3", "Diabetes Mellitus": "2", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "7", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "4", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "4", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "7", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "13", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "7", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "9", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "3", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "5", "Influenza & pneumonia": "8", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "5", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "7", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "7", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "12", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "6", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "7", "Other diseases of intestines": "18", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "6", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "4", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "9", "Arthropathies": "17", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "9", "Soft tissue disorders": "7", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "3", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "3", "Urolithiasis": "3", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "8", "Diseases of male genital organs": "4", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "6", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "30", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "7", "Congenital malformations": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "12", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "16", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "9", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "5", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "5", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "3", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "6", "Examination and investigation": "9", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "15", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "4", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS5 7PD": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "5180", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "7", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "8", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "8", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "5", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "6", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "5", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "8", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "4", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "5", "Other diseases of intestines": "12", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "6", "Arthropathies": "11", "Dorsopathies": "6", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "5", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "4", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "19", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "5", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "10", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "6", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "6", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "10", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS21 6DG": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6313", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "8", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "9", "Anaemias": "7", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "10", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "6", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "7", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "6", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "6", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "9", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "4", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "6", "Other diseases of intestines": "14", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "7", "Arthropathies": "13", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "7", "Soft tissue disorders": "5", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "6", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "23", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "5", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "10", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "12", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "7", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "7", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "12", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS13 0JP": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3008", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "4", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "4", "Anaemias": "3", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "5", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "3", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "4", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "7", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "3", "Arthropathies": "6", "Dorsopathies": "3", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "11", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "3", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "3", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "6", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS37 4AA": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4505", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "10", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "17", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS23 3HQ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4783", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "8", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "11", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "10", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "5", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "18", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "9", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS23 4JP": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4175", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "9", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "15", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS16 6UG": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3857", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "9", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "8", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "14", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS37 4AX": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "5334", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "7", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "8", "Anaemias": "6", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "8", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "5", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "6", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "5", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "8", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "4", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "5", "Other diseases of intestines": "12", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "6", "Arthropathies": "11", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "6", "Soft tissue disorders": "5", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "5", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "4", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "20", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "5", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "10", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "6", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "6", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "10", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS30 5JZ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "2763", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "4", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "4", "Anaemias": "3", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "4", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "3", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "4", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "2", "Other diseases of intestines": "6", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "3", "Arthropathies": "6", "Dorsopathies": "3", "Soft tissue disorders": "2", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "10", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "2", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "3", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "3", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "5", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS13 7JD": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3308", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "4", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "5", "Anaemias": "3", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "5", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "5", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "7", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "7", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "12", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "6", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS13 8LD": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4357", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "16", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS15 8NJ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4650", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "10", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "17", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "9", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS22 8AG": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3523", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "5", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "5", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "8", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "7", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "13", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS5 9QY": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3783", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "8", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "8", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "14", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS15 1WW": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "8895", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "5", "Certain bacterial diseases": "5", "Viral infections characterized by skin & mucous mem. lesns.": "1", "Other viral diseases": "4", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "8", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "7", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "12", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "13", "Anaemias": "9", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "3", "Disorders of thyroid gland": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "2", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "7", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "2", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "4", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "4", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "7", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "14", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "3", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "8", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "10", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "3", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "5", "Influenza & pneumonia": "9", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "6", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "7", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "3", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "8", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "13", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "6", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "8", "Other diseases of intestines": "20", "Diseases of liver": "2", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "7", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "4", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "10", "Arthropathies": "19", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "10", "Soft tissue disorders": "8", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "3", "Diseases of the kidney": "3", "Renal failure": "3", "Urolithiasis": "3", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "8", "Diseases of male genital organs": "4", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "6", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "4", "Complications of labour and delivery": "33", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "8", "Congenital malformations": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "14", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "17", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "3", "General symptoms & signs": "10", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "6", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "6", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "3", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "3", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "4", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "7", "Examination and investigation": "10", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "17", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "4", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS15 4EJ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4888", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "7", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "8", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "11", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "6", "Arthropathies": "10", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "5", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "4", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "18", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "9", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS24 7DX": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4468", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "16", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS10 6DF": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4337", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "16", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS16 2JD": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "9246", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "5", "Certain bacterial diseases": "5", "Viral infections characterized by skin & mucous mem. lesns.": "1", "Other viral diseases": "4", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "9", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "7", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "12", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "14", "Anaemias": "10", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "3", "Disorders of thyroid gland": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "2", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "8", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "2", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Extrapyramidal & movement disorders (incl. Parkinsonism).": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "4", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "5", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "8", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "15", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "3", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "8", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "10", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "4", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "3", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "5", "Influenza & pneumonia": "9", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "6", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "8", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "3", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "8", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "14", "Diseases of appendix": "2", "Hernia": "7", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "8", "Other diseases of intestines": "21", "Diseases of liver": "2", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "7", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "4", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "11", "Arthropathies": "20", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "10", "Soft tissue disorders": "8", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "3", "Diseases of the kidney": "3", "Renal failure": "3", "Urolithiasis": "3", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "9", "Diseases of male genital organs": "4", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "7", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "4", "Complications of labour and delivery": "34", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "8", "Congenital malformations": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "14", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "18", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "3", "General symptoms & signs": "10", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "6", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "6", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "2", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "3", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "3", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "3", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "4", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "7", "Examination and investigation": "10", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "17", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "4", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS9 2HL": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "2817", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "4", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "4", "Anaemias": "3", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "4", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "3", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "4", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "6", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "3", "Arthropathies": "6", "Dorsopathies": "3", "Soft tissue disorders": "2", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "10", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "2", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "3", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "3", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "5", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS7 8SA": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "7915", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "7", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "11", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "12", "Anaemias": "8", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "3", "Diabetes Mellitus": "2", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "6", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "4", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "4", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "6", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "13", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "7", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "9", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "3", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "8", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "5", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "7", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "7", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "12", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "6", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "7", "Other diseases of intestines": "18", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "6", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "4", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "9", "Arthropathies": "17", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "9", "Soft tissue disorders": "7", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "3", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "7", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "6", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "29", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "7", "Congenital malformations": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "12", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "15", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "9", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "5", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "5", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "3", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "6", "Examination and investigation": "9", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "15", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "4", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS15 3HY": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "8591", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "5", "Certain bacterial diseases": "5", "Viral infections characterized by skin & mucous mem. lesns.": "1", "Other viral diseases": "4", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "8", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "12", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "13", "Anaemias": "9", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "3", "Diabetes Mellitus": "2", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "7", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "2", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "4", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "4", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "7", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "14", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "3", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "8", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "9", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "3", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "5", "Influenza & pneumonia": "9", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "5", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "7", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "3", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "8", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "13", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "6", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "8", "Other diseases of intestines": "19", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "6", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "4", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "10", "Arthropathies": "18", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "10", "Soft tissue disorders": "7", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "3", "Diseases of the kidney": "3", "Renal failure": "3", "Urolithiasis": "3", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "8", "Diseases of male genital organs": "4", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "6", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "4", "Complications of labour and delivery": "31", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "7", "Congenital malformations": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "13", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "17", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "3", "General symptoms & signs": "9", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "6", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "5", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "3", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "3", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "6", "Examination and investigation": "9", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "16", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "4", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS8 3EU": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6492", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "9", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "10", "Anaemias": "7", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "10", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "6", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "7", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "7", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "6", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "10", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "5", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "6", "Other diseases of intestines": "15", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "7", "Arthropathies": "14", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "7", "Soft tissue disorders": "6", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "6", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "24", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "6", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "10", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "12", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "7", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "7", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "12", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS3 4AT": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4793", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "8", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "11", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "10", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "5", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "18", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "4", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "9", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS4 2QJ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4359", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "16", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS20 0DL": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "2610", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "1", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "4", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "4", "Anaemias": "3", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "4", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "3", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "1", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "2", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "4", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "2", "Other diseases of intestines": "6", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "3", "Arthropathies": "6", "Dorsopathies": "3", "Soft tissue disorders": "2", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "2", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "10", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "2", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "3", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "3", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "5", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS40 5EL": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "17345", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "10", "Certain bacterial diseases": "9", "Viral infections characterized by skin & mucous mem. lesns.": "1", "Other viral diseases": "7", "Mycoses": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "16", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "7", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "9", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "13", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "12", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "23", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "26", "Anaemias": "18", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "6", "Disorders of thyroid gland": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "3", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "14", "Dementia": "1", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "3", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "2", "Other degenerative diseases (incl. Alzheimer).": "1", "Extrapyramidal & movement disorders (incl. Parkinsonism).": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "3", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "8", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "9", "Cerebral palsy & other paralytic syndromes": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "14", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "27", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "5", "Rheumatic heart disease": "1", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "16", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "19", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "7", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "4", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "6", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "2", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "10", "Influenza & pneumonia": "18", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "11", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "6", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "14", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "5", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "16", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "26", "Diseases of appendix": "3", "Hernia": "12", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "15", "Other diseases of intestines": "39", "Diseases of peritoneum": "1", "Diseases of liver": "3", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "13", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "8", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "20", "Dermatitis and eczema": "1", "Papulosquamous disorders (including Psoriasis)": "1", "Urticaria and erythems": "1", "Arthropathies": "37", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "2", "Dorsopathies": "19", "Soft tissue disorders": "15", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "5", "Other disorders of the musculoskeletal system & conn. tiss.": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "5", "Renal failure": "6", "Urolithiasis": "5", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "16", "Diseases of male genital organs": "8", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "13", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "7", "Complications of labour and delivery": "64", "Delivery": "2", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "15", "Congenital malformations": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "27", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "33", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "6", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. speech & voice": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "19", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "11", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "3", "Injuries to the head": "11", "Injuries to the neck": "1", "Injuries to the thorax": "2", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "2", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "3", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "4", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "6", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "5", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "5", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Burns and corrosions": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "7", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "13", "Examination and investigation": "19", "Potential health hazards related to communicable diseases": "1", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "32", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "8", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1", "Persons with potential health hazards related to family": "1"}}, "BS2 0AN": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3771", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "8", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "8", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "14", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS6 6DF": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6347", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "9", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "9", "Anaemias": "7", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "10", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "6", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "7", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "6", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "6", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "9", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "5", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "6", "Other diseases of intestines": "14", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "7", "Arthropathies": "13", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "7", "Soft tissue disorders": "5", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "6", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "23", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "6", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "10", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "12", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "7", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "7", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "12", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS8 2PU": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6553", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "9", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "10", "Anaemias": "7", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "10", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "6", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "7", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "7", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "6", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "10", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "5", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "6", "Other diseases of intestines": "15", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "8", "Arthropathies": "14", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "7", "Soft tissue disorders": "6", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "6", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "24", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "6", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "10", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "13", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "7", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "7", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "12", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS4 1WH": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "2662", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "1", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "4", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "4", "Anaemias": "3", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "4", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "3", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "1", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "2", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "4", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "2", "Other diseases of intestines": "6", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "3", "Arthropathies": "6", "Dorsopathies": "3", "Soft tissue disorders": "2", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "10", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "2", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "3", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "3", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "5", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS10 6AF": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3440", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "5", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "5", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "5", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "8", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "7", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "13", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "6", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS35 2AT": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3146", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "4", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "5", "Anaemias": "3", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "5", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "3", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "5", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "7", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "7", "Dorsopathies": "3", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "12", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "3", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "3", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "6", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS7 9EG": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "20", "diagnoses": {}}, "BS35 4JF": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "1722", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "1", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "2", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "3", "Anaemias": "2", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "1", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "3", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "2", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "1", "Influenza & pneumonia": "2", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "1", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "2", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "3", "Hernia": "1", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "2", "Other diseases of intestines": "4", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "1", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "2", "Arthropathies": "4", "Dorsopathies": "2", "Soft tissue disorders": "1", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "2", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "1", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "6", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "1", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "2", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "1", "Injuries to the head": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "1", "Examination and investigation": "2", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "3", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS34 8UE": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6569", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "9", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "10", "Anaemias": "7", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "10", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "6", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "7", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "7", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "6", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "10", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "5", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "6", "Other diseases of intestines": "15", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "8", "Arthropathies": "14", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "7", "Soft tissue disorders": "6", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "6", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "24", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "6", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "10", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "13", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "7", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "7", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "12", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS4 2DF": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3489", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "5", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "5", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "8", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "7", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "13", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS32 4DS": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "2170", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "1", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "3", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "3", "Anaemias": "2", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "3", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "2", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "1", "Influenza & pneumonia": "2", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "1", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "2", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "3", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "2", "Other diseases of intestines": "5", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "2", "Arthropathies": "5", "Dorsopathies": "2", "Soft tissue disorders": "2", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "2", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "8", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "2", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "2", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "1", "Injuries to the head": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "2", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "4", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS30 8HS": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4532", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "10", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "17", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS9 4HT": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4203", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "9", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "15", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS6 6AU": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "8266", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "5", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Viral infections characterized by skin & mucous mem. lesns.": "1", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "8", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "11", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "12", "Anaemias": "9", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "3", "Diabetes Mellitus": "2", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "7", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "4", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "4", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "7", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "13", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "7", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "9", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "3", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "5", "Influenza & pneumonia": "8", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "5", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "7", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "3", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "8", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "12", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "6", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "7", "Other diseases of intestines": "19", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "6", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "4", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "9", "Arthropathies": "17", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "9", "Soft tissue disorders": "7", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "3", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "3", "Urolithiasis": "3", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "8", "Diseases of male genital organs": "4", "Disorders of breast": "1", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "6", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "4", "Complications of labour and delivery": "30", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "7", "Congenital malformations": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "13", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "16", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "9", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "5", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "5", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "3", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "3", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Injuries to the ankle & foot": "1", "Effects of foreign body entering through natural orifice": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Other and unspecified effects of external causes": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "6", "Examination and investigation": "9", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "15", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "4", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS20 7QA": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3865", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "5", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "6", "Anaemias": "4", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "3", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "3", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "6", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "4", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "6", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "9", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "4", "Arthropathies": "8", "Dorsopathies": "4", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "14", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "4", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "4", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "7", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS9 1JN": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "1861", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "1", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "2", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "3", "Anaemias": "2", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "3", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "2", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "1", "Influenza & pneumonia": "2", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "1", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "2", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "3", "Hernia": "1", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "2", "Other diseases of intestines": "4", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "1", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "2", "Arthropathies": "4", "Dorsopathies": "2", "Soft tissue disorders": "2", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "2", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "1", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "7", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "2", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "2", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "1", "Injuries to the head": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "1", "Examination and investigation": "2", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "3", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS16 7AL": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4575", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "5", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "10", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "17", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "9", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS37 5UY": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "1223", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "1", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "2", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "2", "Anaemias": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "1", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "2", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "1", "Influenza & pneumonia": "1", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "1", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "2", "Hernia": "1", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "1", "Other diseases of intestines": "3", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "1", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "1", "Arthropathies": "3", "Dorsopathies": "1", "Soft tissue disorders": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "1", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "1", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "4", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "1", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "1", "Injuries to the head": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "1", "Examination and investigation": "1", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "2", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS22 6AJ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6034", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "3", "Certain bacterial diseases": "3", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "8", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "9", "Anaemias": "6", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "5", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "5", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "10", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "5", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "7", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "3", "Influenza & pneumonia": "6", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "5", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "5", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "9", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "4", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "5", "Other diseases of intestines": "14", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "4", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "7", "Arthropathies": "13", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "7", "Soft tissue disorders": "5", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "6", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "4", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "22", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "5", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "9", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "12", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "7", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "4", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "7", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "11", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3"}}, "BS32 9DS": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "6926", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "4", "Certain bacterial diseases": "4", "Other viral diseases": "3", "Malignant neoplasm of lip-oral cavity and pharynx": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "6", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of mesothelial and soft tissue": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of eye, brain & other parts of CNS": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "5", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "9", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "10", "Anaemias": "7", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "2", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "6", "Other organic including symptomatic mental disorders": "1", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Schizophrenia, schizotypal and delusional disorders": "1", "Mood [affective] disorders": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "3", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "3", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "6", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "11", "Glaucoma": "1", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "2", "Hypertensive diseases": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "6", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "8", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "3", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "2", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "2", "Other & unspecified disorders of the circulatory system": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "4", "Influenza & pneumonia": "7", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "4", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "3", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "6", "Lung diseases due to external agents": "1", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "2", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "6", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "10", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "5", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "6", "Other diseases of intestines": "16", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "5", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "3", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "8", "Arthropathies": "15", "Systemic connective tissue disorders": "1", "Dorsopathies": "8", "Soft tissue disorders": "6", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "2", "Diseases of the kidney": "2", "Renal failure": "2", "Urolithiasis": "2", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "7", "Diseases of male genital organs": "3", "Inflammatory diseases of female pelvic organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "5", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "3", "Complications of labour and delivery": "25", "Delivery": "1", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "6", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "11", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "13", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "3", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "2", "General symptoms & signs": "8", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "5", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "4", "Injuries to the thorax": "1", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "2", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "2", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "2", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "2", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "3", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "5", "Examination and investigation": "8", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "13", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "3", "Persons encountering health services in other circs.": "1"}}, "BS7 0UE": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "3043", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "4", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "5", "Anaemias": "3", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "5", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "3", "Other forms of heart disease": "3", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "3", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "2", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "3", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "3", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "5", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "3", "Other diseases of intestines": "7", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "3", "Arthropathies": "6", "Dorsopathies": "3", "Soft tissue disorders": "3", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "3", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "11", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "3", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "5", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "6", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "3", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "2", "Injuries to the head": "2", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "3", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "6", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS23 3SJ": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "2215", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "1", "Certain bacterial diseases": "1", "Other viral diseases": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "1", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "3", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "3", "Anaemias": "2", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "2", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "1", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "1", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "2", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "4", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "2", "Other forms of heart disease": "2", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "1", "Influenza & pneumonia": "2", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "1", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "1", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "2", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "2", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "3", "Hernia": "2", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "2", "Other diseases of intestines": "5", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "2", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "1", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "3", "Arthropathies": "5", "Dorsopathies": "2", "Soft tissue disorders": "2", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "2", "Diseases of male genital organs": "1", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "2", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "1", "Complications of labour and delivery": "8", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "2", "Congenital malformations": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "3", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "4", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "1", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "2", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "1", "Injuries to the head": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "1", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "2", "Examination and investigation": "2", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "4", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "1"}}, "BS2 8HW": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "1", "diagnoses": {}}, "BS1 3EA": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "4353", "diagnoses": {"Intestinal infectious diseases": "2", "Certain bacterial diseases": "2", "Other viral diseases": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of digestive organs": "4", "Malignant neoplasms of respiratory & intrathoracic organs": "2", "Malignant neoplasms of skin": "2", "Malignant neoplasm of breast": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of female genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of male genital organs": "1", "Malignant neoplasms of urinary tract": "1", "Malignant neoplsm. of thyroid and oth. endo. Glands etc": "3", "Malignant neoplasms of lymphoid, haematopoietic & rel. tiss.": "6", "In situ & benign neoplasms and others of uncertainty": "7", "Anaemias": "5", "Diseases of the blood and blood-forming organs": "1", "Diabetes Mellitus": "1", "Endocrine nutritional and metabolic diseases": "4", "Mental and behavioural disorders due to psychoactive subst.": "1", "Neurotic, behavioural & personality disorders": "1", "Demyelinating diseases (incl Multiple Sclerosis) of the CNS.": "1", "Epilepsy, migraine & other episodic disorders": "2", "Other diseases & disorders of the nervous syst.": "2", "Other disorders of the eye etc": "4", "Disorders of lens (including cataracts)": "7", "Diseases of the ear and mastoid process": "1", "Ischaemic heart diseases": "4", "Pulmonary heart disease & diseases of pulmonary circulation": "1", "Other forms of heart disease": "5", "Cerebrovascular diseases": "2", "Diseases of arteries, arterioles & capillaries": "1", "Diseases of veins & lymphatic system nec.": "1", "Acute upper respiratory infections": "2", "Influenza & pneumonia": "4", "Other acute lower respiratory infections": "3", "Other diseases of upper respiratory tract": "2", "Chronic lower respiratory diseases": "4", "Other diseases of the respiratory system": "1", "Diseases of oral cavity, salivary glands & jaws": "4", "Diseases of oesophagus, stomach & duodenum": "7", "Diseases of appendix": "1", "Hernia": "3", "Noninfective enteritis & colitis": "4", "Other diseases of intestines": "10", "Diseases of liver": "1", "Disorders of gall bladder, biliary tract & pancreas": "3", "Other diseases of the digestive system": "2", "Other infections and disorders of the skin": "5", "Arthropathies": "9", "Dorsopathies": "5", "Soft tissue disorders": "4", "Osteopathies and chondropathies": "1", "Diseases of the kidney": "1", "Renal failure": "1", "Urolithiasis": "1", "Other diseases of the urinary system": "4", "Diseases of male genital organs": "2", "Noninflammatory disorders of female genital tract": "3", "Pregnancy with abortive outcome": "2", "Complications of labour and delivery": "16", "Other conditions originating in the perinatal period": "4", "Congenital malformations": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. the circulatory/respiratory system": "7", "Symptoms & signs inv. the digestive system & abdomen": "8", "Symptoms & signs inv. the skin & subcutaneous tissue": "1", "Symptoms & signs inv. the nervous & musculoskeletal sys.": "2", "Symptoms & signs involving the urinary system": "2", "Symptoms & signs inv. Cognition perception etc.": "1", "General symptoms & signs": "5", "Unknown & unspecified causes of morbidity": "3", "Abnormal findings of bodily fluids or samples without diag.": "1", "Abnormal findings on diagnostic imaging/function studies": "1", "Injuries to the head": "3", "Injuries to abdomen, lower back, lumbar spine & pelvis": "1", "Injuries to the shoulder & upper arm": "1", "Injuries to the elbow & forearm": "1", "Injuries to the wrist & hand": "1", "Injuries to the hip & thigh": "1", "Injuries to the knee & lower leg": "1", "Poisonings by drugs medicaments & biological substances": "2", "Complications of surgical & medical care nec.": "3", "Examination and investigation": "5", "Health services in circumstances related to reproduction": "8", "Persons encountering health services for specific care": "2"}}, "BS2 8JP": {"name": "GP", "appointments": "2", "diagnoses": {}}, "BS10 5NB": {"name": "North Bristol NHS Trust", "appointments": "11809", "diagnoses": {}}, "BS1 3NU": {"name": "University Hospitals Bristol NHS Foundation Trust", "appointments": "12169", "diagnoses": {}}}